I am not black I mean that's what the world calls me
but it's not me I didn't
come out of my mother's womb saying hey everybody I'm black no
I was taught to
be black and you were taught to call me that along with
whatever you call
yourself it's just a label see from birth the world force feeds
us these
labels and eventually we all swallow them we digest and accept the
labels never
ever doubting them but there's one problem labels are not you and
labels
are not me labels are just labels but who we truly are
is not skin deep see
when I drive my car no one would ever confuse the car
for me well when I
drive my body why do you confuse me for my body it's
my body get it not me let me
break it down so your bodies are just cars that we operate
and drive around
the dealership we call society decided to label mine the black edition
yours
the Irish or white edition and with no money down 0 %
APR and no test drive we
were forced to own these cars for the rest of our lives
forgive me but I fail
to see the logic or pride in defining myself or judging another
by the
cars we drive because who we truly are is found inside listen
I'm not here
to tell you how science has concluded that genetically we're all mixed
and
race in the human species doesn't exist or how every historian knows
that
race was invented in the 15th century to divide people from each
other and it
is our mission and that is not my opinion that is the
truth in a world
that has sold us fiction please listen labels only distort our vision
which is why half of those watching this will dismiss it or
feel resistance
and conflicted but just remember so did the caterpillar before it broke
through its shell and became the magnificent butterfly well these labels
are our shells and we must do the same thing so we
can finally spread our
wings human beings were not meant to be slapped with labels like
groceries
and supermarkets DNA cannot be regulated by the FDA we were meant
to be free and
only until we remove them all and stop living and thinking so
small will we be
free to see ourselves and each other for who we truly are
base of all this madness and chaos what is the solution we
can love
trying to control the mind is like trying to flatten out water
you just
make more waves